malektips.com 2013-09-23

# MalekTips - Privacy Policy

MalekTips.Com is owned by Andrew Malek of Envision Programming. 

Envision Programming  
attn: MalekTips.Com  
PO Box 11592  
Knoxville, TN 37939-1592

This privacy statement applies to the MalekTips.Com website, and may or may not apply to content provided by third-party providers, advertisements, or external links. 

Note as of July 21, 2012: We are transitioning our e-mail list to a FeedBurner-administered list, with email delivery powered by Google. Privacy policy: <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>. 

Regarding our old e-mail list:If you choose to subscribe to our opt-in E-Mail list, it is our intention to keep your E-Mail address secure. We will not willingly give out your e-mail address to any other party. Your e-mail address will not be willingly given to any advertiser. 

If you choose to provide a comment to us via e-mail or our Contact Us page, your name, e-mail address, and comments will not be willingly provided to any third party unless you give us permission. Requests for help by e-mail, however, may be reprinted in the MalekTips Forums for the benefit of the community, and may be edited for clarity or brevity. 

To allow tip comments, the Disqus service is used. Their privacy policy is at <http://docs.disqus.com/kb/terms-and-policies/>. 

###  Cookies and Advertisements 

Cookies may be sent to your browser from MalekTips. The functions of the cookies include, but are not limited to, the following: recording your username/password, last login, and other information for use of the forums by the forum software, and testing to see if cookies exist. 

MalekTips works with third-party sites to deliver ads. For more information about Burst Media, visit <http://burstmedia.com/privacy.asp>. For more information about ValueClick Media, visit <http://www.valueclickmedia.com/privacy.shtml>. For more information about Google, visit <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>. 

Third-party sites, such as ad networks, may send cookies and web beacons to your browser. These automatically receive your IP address. Third-party sites may also use technology such as JavaScript, Java, and Web Beacons. Usage may be for, among other things, advertisement personalization and tracking. These third party sites, cookies, and web beacons are not under the control of Andrew Malek, Envision Programming, or MalekTips. Please refer to the privacy policies of the aforementioned sites for more information. 

Regarding BurstMedia: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.burstmedia.com/consumer_optout.asp). 

###  Registration for Those Under 13 

Portions of MalekTips may require registration, which may include submitting an e-mail address and/or other personally identifiable information. These portions are not geared towards children, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from those under the age of 13. 

### Newest Tips:

[ Google   
Look Inside Google's Data Centers ](http://malektips.com/google-data-centers-photos.html) [ Sites to Browse - Humor - Pranks   
Make the Internet Safe for Cats  ](http://malektips.com/meowbify-cat-photo-any-site.html) [ Google   
Find Google Blogs, Plus Google on Twitter, FaceBook, Elsewhere  ](http://malektips.com/google-blog-facebook-twitter-plus.html) [ Microsoft Excel 2010   
Stop Accidentally Showing the Ribbon Shortcut Keys  ](http://malektips.com/excel-2010-slash-ribbon-shortcut-keys-menu-disable.html)

### Follow Us!

###  About MalekTips and the Author 

The MalekTips website was created in 1998 by Andrew Malek of Envision Programming. The page's goal is to freely disperse computer-related tips, hints, and informative articles. Tips are organized to be easy to find, and are presented clearly, in easy-to-understand language. MalekTips also provides information and links to public-domain, open source, freeware, shareware, and commercial software available for download.
